JASEEL P V

+91 9746664696 jaseelbavu@gmail.com

A Suitable position with an organization where I can utilize the best of my skills and abilities that fit to my education, skills and experience a place where an encourage and permitted to be an active participant as well vital contribute on development of the company.

SKILLS

PHP, Laravel, Vue.js, Firebase, Bootstrap, Linux, Rest API, MySQL, Javascript, CSS, NoSQL, JQuery, Git, Razorpay, Bagisto, Envoyer, Tailwind CSS, Postman

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Web Developer

Palmate Solutions - 09/2019 to 12/2020

Bangalore, Karnataka

- Lead the team to migrate existing and new projects to Laravel framework.
- Providing guidance to the team to learn Laravel framework and with their works.
- Involved in project development from scratch to deployment.
- Develop and worked on both frontend and backend technologies based on provided design.
- Version control system for tracking and managing changes to the project codes.
- Hands on experience with API like REST API, payment API and Google API.
- Work closely with other developers, designers and product manager.
- Design, develop, document, and debug sites and ensure code reuse and organization.
- Works with R&D department to assist in planning and executing new product development.

Co-Founder/Web Developer

Exam Summary - 01/2015 to 05/2017

Ernamkulam, Kerala

- Work closely with other co-founders about the product development and implementation.
- Gather and refine specifications and requirements based on technical needs.
- Conducted target market research to scope out industry competition and identify advantageous trends.
- Help ensure students have a seamless experience across subjects and grade levels.
- Integrate data from various back-end services and databases.
- Stay plugged into emerging technologies/industry trends and apply them into operations and activities.

EDUCATION

The Oxford College Of Engineering, Bommanahalli

Master Computer Application

Bangalore, India - 08/2017 to 07/2019

Assabah Arts And Science College, Valayamkulam

Bachelor Computer Application

Changaramkulam, India - 08/2013 to 05/2016

Govt. H S S, Kodumunda

HSC - Computer Science

Pattambi, India - 06/2011 to 03/2013

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Marital Status : Single
Nationality : Indian

Language Known : English, Malayalam

Address : S/o. Bavu P V

Pulamanthol Valappil House, Chazhiyattiri Post,

Palakkad Dt-Kerala-679535